The man. The legend. His story. His words.
Gascoigne is a documentary film directed by Jane Preston.
A feature length, theatrical documentary on the life of Paul Gascoigne, one of the greatest
footballers that ever lived: delving deep into his psyche, vulnerabilities, fears and triumphs.
Self, played by Paul Gascoigne.
Self, played by Gary Lineker.
Self, played by José Mourinho.
Self, played by Wayne Rooney.
Self (archive footage), played by Vinnie Jones.
Self (archive footage), played by Diego Maradona.
Gascoigne is a 2015 documentary about the English footballer Paul Gascoigne.
The film explores themes of sports, alcoholism, football (soccer).
The tone is thought_provoking.